sunrisekings.com 2011-11-20

# SunriseKings.com | HD Porn | Worlds Best High Definition Porn Movies

** PRIVACY POLICY**

PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY STATEMENT CAREFULLY. BY YOUR SUBSCRIPTION TO AND USE OF THIS SITE YOU WILL BE EXPRESSLY SIGNIFYING THAT YOU AGREE WITH THE POLICIES AND PRACTICES SET FORTH IN THE PRESENT PRIVACY POLICY STATEMENT AND THAT YOU ASSENT TO THE USE OF ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION THAT YOU SUPPLY OR THAT IS COLLECTED ABOUT YOU AS DETAILED IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY STATEMENT. 

IF YOU DO NOT EXPRESSLY AGREE WITH ALL OF THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY STATEMENT YOU SHOULD NOT SUBSCRIBE TO OR USE THIS SITE. 

Your privacy is of utmost importance to us. This Privacy Policy governs your use of this website and all of our other websites including, but not limited to,  [sunrisekings.com](http://www.sunrisekings.com/) (the "Sites", "we" or "us"). As noted below, please be aware that we may change our Privacy Policy in the future and it is your obligation to review this Privacy Policy from time to time and the effective date listed with it.

**USE**

This is an **adult site** that expressly and strictly limits its membership to adults. This site does not knowingly seek or collect any personal information or data from persons under the age of 18. All persons under the age of 18 are strictly prohibited from accessing or viewing the contents on this site without exception. If you are under the age of 18 and/or under the age of majority in the jurisdiction you reside and from which you access the website, then your account will be terminated without notice or delay. 

**INFORMATION COLLECTED FROM SUBSCRIBERS**

Any customer that joins/signs up as a subscriber of the site will be required to provide personal information as well as demographic information which may include the subscriber's name, physical address, e-mail address, zip code, country, username, and password. The site collects any and all such information and includes it in its customer database. In addition, other information such as IP address(es), referring website information, browser information, and other related data may be collected. 

**USE OF PERSONAL SUBSCRIBER INFORMATION**

If the site features or conducts any special events, special promotions or offers, contests or polls, a subscriber of the site may be asked to provide information in order to participate, if the subscriber voluntarily provides that information, all such information may be collected by the site and included in its customer database. 

If a subscriber sends any personal communication or correspondence by any means, to the site, or any of its employees, agents or representatives, the site may collect the information regarding that communication and include that information in its customer database. 

The site may also automatically collect traffic and click-through data as well as information regarding the online behavior of subscribers by the use of "cookies" or other programming means – any information about subscribers collected by the site through the use of cookies or other programming means will generally not be associable to the specific user in any way. 

**DISCLAIMER**

By the subscriber's use of the site, the subscriber expressly agrees that the site may use any personal information that has been provided by the subscriber or that has been collected by the site about the subscriber for any purpose, including without limitation, technical, administrative, research and development, customer administration, marketing, trading of personal data, age verification, promotional and advertising use by the site or third parties authorized to use the information by the site. 

By the subscriber's use of the site, the subscriber expressly agrees that the site may, in its sole discretion share, disclose, transfer, rent, license or sell any of the personal information about subscribers that it has gathered or collected with affiliated or unaffiliated third parties. 

All personal information about a subscriber may be collected by a third-party web service provider that has an advertising banner or link on the site. 

The site is not responsible or liable for the use of any information that a subscriber may provide, or that is gathered by third-party websites that have banner ads or links on the site. The site shall not be responsible for the privacy policy or the content of other such websites. This site does not control, monitor or endorse the information gathering practices or privacy policies of any of those third-party websites. 

Whenever applicable, each subscriber should seek to read the privacy policy of any third-party website provider that has an advertising banner, advertises or has a link on the site. 

All information collected may be shared when necessary to comply with applicable law and /or to cooperate with law enforcement agencies and the courts/tribunals. 

A subscriber’s IP address may be used to diagnose problems with the server and all other technical issues and to administer the websites. 

**SECURITY OF INFORMATION COLLECTED BY THE SITE**

The site has adopted and implemented reasonable and technologically feasible procedures for maintaining the security, accuracy and integrity of all personal information relating to subscribers that is collected by the site. 

While the website uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. All subscribers should consider any information provided to or collected by the site as non-confidential, and consequently the site assumes no liability or responsibility if any information relating to any subscriber is intercepted and/or used by an unintended recipient. 

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. The website uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. 

**FINANCIAL INFORMATION**

All financial data will only be shared with the site’s third party processors in order to initiate and complete any orders placed on your account. All credit card transactions and such are processed with industry standard encryption through third party processors. Said processors only use your information for that purpose. All financial data and information shall be considered private information and will not be shared by the site with third parties except with your authorization or when necessary to carry out all and any transactions requested by the user with the understanding that such transactions may be subject to rules, terms, conditions and policies of a third party. All such information provided to a third party and all transactions are not governed by this Privacy Policy. All such information provided to a third party is subject to their terms and conditions. 

Subscriber’s e-mail address may be used by the site to communicate special offers and other relevant information such as new services, subscription information, etc. In addition, there may be occasions when a subscriber will be presented with special offers either from the operators of the site or from third-party service or content providers, which may include consent to receive e-mail solicitations, communications, newsletters, commercial advertising, or other promotional or special event materials. 

**CHANGES/MODIFICATIONS TO PRIVACY POLICY**

This privacy policy may be changed, modified or edited at any time. It is the subscriber’s responsibility to verify the Privacy Policy intermittently to see if there has been any change. All changes to the privacy policy shall be in effect thirty days after it is posted, unless the terms of the privacy policy indicate otherwise. 

**TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF MEMBERSHIP**

a) Rights

Each subscriber should carefully read each of the terms and conditions of membership for the site. By accepting membership to this site, you are unconditionally accepting all of those terms and conditions. Some of those terms and conditions may also affect the right of this site to use information that it has gathered from subscribers.

b) Member Account, Password and Security

As part of the registration process, you will select a unique user name and password which you must provide in order to gain access to the non-public portion of a Site. You represent and warrant that you will not disclose to any other person your unique user name and password and that you will not provide access to any Site to anyone who is below the age of majority in your jurisdiction. You are solely responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your user name and password and are fully responsible for all activities that occur under your user name and password. You agree to (1) immediately notify SunriseKings of any unauthorized use of your user name and password or any other breach of security, and (2) ensure that you exit from your account at the end of each session.

c) Fees

You agree to pay all membership fees when due. SunriseKings posts the current membership fees for each Site as part of the registration process. SunriseKings reserves the right to change any Site's membership fees at any time, with or without prior notice to you. At the time of registration, you must select a payment method. SunriseKings reserves the right to contract with a third party to process all payments. Such third party may impose additional terms and conditions governing payment processing. Your account will be deemed past due if it is not paid in full by the payment due date. If your account become past due, you agree to pay interest on the past due amount at a monthly rate of 1.5%, or the highest amount allowed by law, whichever is lower, compounded daily, plus any additional collection costs, credits, charge backs and attorneys fees. Your card issuer agreement may contain additional terms with respect to your rights and liabilities as a card holder. You are responsible for reimbursing SunriseKings for all credit card charge backs, dishonored checks and any related charges.

d) Refund Policy

SunriseKings does not provide cash refunds. We may, however, grant credits in the form of free monthly memberships to resolve customer service issues. The billing system used by SunriseKings or our authorized agents provides extensive credit card fraud protection measures and our Sites include many features to protect users from accidental charges. Therefore, refunds to your credit card will be provided only under the rarest of circumstances such as persistent technical problems originating with our equipment.

**INDEMNITY**

You agree to indemnify SunriseKings against any and all claims, liabilities, and costs, including reasonable attorneys’ fees, reasonably incurred in the defense of any claim or suit arising out of or otherwise related to these Terms and Conditions, including without limitation, any breach by you of this Agreement. SUnriseKings shall promptly notify you by electronic mail of any such claim or suit, and cooperate fully (at your expense) in the defense of such claim or suit. SUnriseKings may participate in the defense of such claim or defense at its own expense, and choose its own legal counsel, but is not obligated to do so
